NIGHTCLUBBING Archive by Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong 1970-2009 (Bulk 1975-1980) MSS.305
Fales Library and Special Collections
NIGHTCLUBBING Archive by Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong
1970-2009
1975-1980
Fales Library and Special Collections
Ivers, Pat
Armstrong, Emily
MSS.305
16 Cubic Feet
161 U-matic
24 Betacam
26 Half_Inch_Video_Reel
21 MiniDV
NIGHTCLUBBING was a weekly cable television show produced by video artists Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong. The NIGHTCLUBBING Archive is a collection of videorecordings featuring live footage filmed between 1975 and 1980 that captures the burgeoning punk scene in nightclubs around New York City.
Biographical Note
Pat Ivers attended New York University's Tisch School of the Arts before working at Manhattan Cable TV's Public Access Department. She began documenting New York City's downtown nightclub scene in the 1970s, working with Nam Juin Paik and other video artists, as well as the Metropolis Video collective and Emily Armstrong. In the 1980s Ivers was instrumental in the creation of the Corporate and Cable Communications Program (now The Media Arts and Technology Department) at the Borough of Manhattan Community College (BMCC) of The City University of New York (CUNY). She began working for ABC Sports in the 1990s and is currently a Producer/Editor at WPIX.
Emily Armstrong scheduled, produced, and promoted television programs as a coordinator in Manhattan Cable TV's Public Access Department in the 1970s. Together with Pat Ivers, a fellow MCTV employee, Armstrong began documenting New York City's downtown nightclub scene to present on the weekly cable television show NIGHTCLUBBING. Armstrong designed and ran the Professional Video Training Program (PROVIT), which retrained thousands of NYC trade union media professionals in new digital technologies. She also worked as a New York Foundation for the Arts (NYFA) Video Artist-In-Residence in the public school system.
Sources:
Go Nightclubbing (www.gonightclubbing.com/index.html)
Historical Note
NIGHTCLUBBING, a weekly cable television show produced by video artists Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong, debuted in 1979. The show was comprised of live footage filmed between 1975 and 1980 by Ivers and Armstrong that captures the burgeoning punk scene in nightclubs around New York City, including CBGB, Mudd Club, and Danceteria. The recordings feature dynamic performances by Bad Brains, Ballistic Kisses, Max Blagg, Blondie, Bush Tetras, John Cale, Contortions, Cramps, Dead Boys, Dead Kennedys, DNA, Go Go's, The Heartbreakers with Richard Hell, Richard Hell and the Voidoids, Levi and the Rockats, The Lounge Lizards, Offs, Iggy Pop, Pylon, Strange Party, The Stilettos with Tish and Snooky, Suburbs, Suicide, Teenage Jesus and the Jerks, Talking Heads, and many others.
Sources:
Bedford+Bowery: Nightclubbing (http://bedfordandbowery.com/category/nightclubbing/)
Go Nightclubbing (http://www.gonightclubbing.com/history.htm)
Conditions Governing Access
Materials are open to researchers. Please contact the Fales Library and Special Collections, fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Provenance
The Fales Library purchased the Nightclubbing Archive by Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong from Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong in 2010.
Arrangement
This arrangement retains the collection's original order. Titles of the videos derive from the titles provided by Ivers and Armstrong. The videos are arranged chronologically, then alphabetically, in the following series:
Series I: Performances
Series I contains live performances recorded by Ivers and Armstrong for the weekly cable television show NIGHTCLUBBING. The footage captures various artists and musicians performing in nightclubs around New York City between 1976 and 1980. This series also includes undated recordings as well as later recordings from 1997 and 2003.
Series II: Interviews
Series II contains video interviews with various musicians, performance artists, critics, and writers involved in the New York City punk scene. Many of the videos are undated. The dated interviews were all made in the 2000s except for one recording from 1977.
Series III: The Come-On's
The seven videos in Series III comprise two shoots and rough edits of The Come-On's video installation project. The project allowed participants to select to view a tape of a performer, or "seducer," in a photo booth. Each tape featured a musician or artist from the downtown scene who attempted to "seduce" the viewer.
Series IV: Narrative Tapes
The six videos in Series IV comprise narrative tapes, which functioned as the precursor to modern music videos. In each narrative tape, an artist's performance is accompanied by thematically relevant stories, images, and video clips.
Series V: Video Lounge
The nineteen videos in Series V contain Video Lounge footage captured by Ivers and Armstrong. The artists created the Video Lounge format after being commissioned to design a video installation for the opening of the Danceteria nightclub in 1980. Video Lounge became a permanent feature at Danceteria but Ivers and Armstrong also included the format in the NIGHTCLUBBING television series, which showed video art, various video clips and footage, and musical performances.
Series VI: Nightclubbing
The sixteen videos in Series VI contain episodes of the NIGHTCLUBBING television series that was broadcast as a local television show in New York City and was also screened at late night viewings at the Anthology Film Archives. While the majority of these recordings are undated, the dated videos were made during 1975-1980.
Scope and Content
The NIGHTCLUBBING Archive by Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong is a collection of videorecordings produced by video artists Pat Ivers and Emily Armstrong for the weekly cable television show NIGHTCLUBBING. The videos feature live footage filmed between 1975 and 1980 that captures the burgeoning punk scene in nightclubs around New York City. The videorecordings vary by type and include live performances captured for the television show; interviews with various musicians, performance artists, critics, and writers; a video installation project; narrative tapes; Video Lounge footage; and episodes of the NIGHTCLUBBING television series.
Related Material at Fales Library and Special Collections
Peter Dougherty Collection (MSS.213)
Downtown Flyers and Invitations (MSS.119)
Richard Hell Papers (MSS.140)
April Palmieri Papers (MSS.115)
Amos Poe Papers (MSS.203)
David Wojnarowicz Papers (MSS.092)
Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
Access copies for some materials are available by appointment for reading room viewing and listening only. Please contact fales.library@nyu.edu, 212-998-2596.
Lower East Side (New York, N.Y.) -- Fiction.; Artists -- New York (N.Y.); Cable television; Cable television -- Access; Music |z New York (State) |z New York |x Performance |x History.; Punk rock music.; Avant-garde (Music); Downtown Collection.; Contortions (Musical group); Cramps (Musical group); Dead Boys (Musical group); Dead Kennedys (Musical group); DNA (Musical group); Bad Brains (Musical group); Blondie (Musical group); Bush Tetras (Musical group); Lounge Lizards (Musical group); Talking Heads (Musical group); Teenage Jesus and the Jerks (Musical group); Suicide (Musical group); Levi and the Rockats (Musical group); Go Go's (Musical group); Iggy, Pop, 1947-; Offs (Musical group); Ramones (Musical group); White, James Chance, 1953-; Hell, Richard; Lindsay, Arto; Pylon (Musical group); Lunch, Lydia; Suburbs (Musical group)
- Series I: Performances
  Scope and Content
  Series I contains live performances recorded by Ivers and Armstrong for the weekly cable television show NIGHTCLUBBING. The footage captures various artists and musicians performing in nightclubs around New York City between 1976 and 1980. This series also includes undated recordings as well as later recordings from 1997 and 2003.
  - Sidewalk Café Interviews at Upper East Side NYC, 1976; ID: 305.0146 (Box 8, Media ID: 305.0146, Box 31, Dvd 305.0146_a)
    Existence and Location of Copies
    DVD access copy available.
    Conditions Governing Access
    Currently available.
    Physical Characteristics and Technical Requirements
    Black & White, Sound
    Duration: 33 minutes
    Original format: 1/2" open reel
  - Friends Forever at Bob Fass's Loft, Summer 1976; ID: 305.0120 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0120, Box 31, Dvd 305.0120_a)
    Color, Sound
    Duration: 26 minutes
  - Dead Boys at CBGB, October 1977; ID: 305.0001 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0001, Box Shared Fales 135, Dvd 305.0001_a)
    Duration: 53 minutes
    Original format: 3/4" Umatic
  - Dead Boys at CBGB, October 1977; ID: 305.0002 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0002, Box Shared Fales 135, Dvd 305.0002_a)
    Duration: 39 minutes
  - Foolish Virgins at Max's, October 1977; ID: 305.0003 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0003, Box Shared Fales 135, Dvd 305.0003_a)
    Color / Black & White, Sound
    Duration: 12 minutes
  - Foolish Virgins at Max's, October 1977; ID: 305.0004 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0004, Box Shared Fales 135, Dvd 305.0004_a)
    Duration: 22 minutes
    Original Format: 3/4" Umatic
  - Foolish Virgins at Max's, October 1977; ID: 305.0005 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0005, Box Shared Fales 135, Dvd 305.0005_a)
    Duration: 21 minutes
  - Blitz Benefit Edit at CBGB, May 1978; ID: 305.0006 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0006, Box Shared Fales 135, Dvd 305.0006_a)
    Duration: 57 minutes
  - Blitz Benefit - Cosmo Interview, Two Timers, Corpse Grinders at CBGBs, May 1978; ID: 305.0007 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0007, Box 28, Dvd 305.0007_a)
  - Blitz Benefit - Dead Boys, Idols, Closing Ambience at CBGB, May 1978; ID: 305.0014 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0014, Box 28, Dvd 305.0014_a)
    Duration: 24 minutes
  - Blitz Benefit - Dead Boys with Divine and the Neon Women at CBGB, May 1978; ID: 305.0012 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0012, Box 28, Dvd 305.0012_a)
    Duration: 32 minutes
  - Blitz Benefit - Dead Boys with John Belushi and Jonathan Paley, Helen Wheels Band at CBGB, May 1978; ID: 305.0008 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0008, Box 28, Dvd 305.0008_a)
  - Blitz Benefit edit at CBGB, May 1978; ID: 305.0016 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0016, Box 28, Dvd 305.0016_a)
  - Blitz Benefit edit at CBGB, May 1978; ID: 305.0017 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0017, Box 28, Dvd 305.0017_a)
  - Blitz Benefit edit at CBGB, May 1978; ID: 305.0018 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0018, Box 28, Dvd 305.0018_a)
    Duration: 25 minutes
  - Blitz Benefit - Erasers (no audio), backstage ambience at CBGB, May 1978; ID: 305.0015 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0015, Box 28, Dvd 305.0015_a)
    Duration: 29 minutes
  - Blitz Benefit - Interviews with Cheetah, Norman, Mark Ross, Girls Room Ambience at CBGB, May 1978; ID: 305.0009 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0009, Box 28, Dvd 305.0009_a)
  - Blitz Benefit - Kathy Kurls, Dead Boys at CBGB, May 1978; ID: 305.0011 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0011, Box 28, Dvd 305.0011_a)
  - Blitz Benefit - Leggs McNeill and Tish, Criminals, Kathy Kurls at CBGB, May 1978; ID: 305.0010 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0010, Box 28, Dvd 305.0010_a)
  - Blitz Benefit - Sirius Trixon at CBGB, May 1978; ID: 305.0013 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0013, Box 28, Dvd 305.0013_a)
  - Bicentennial Time Capsules at Philadelphia, July 1978; ID: 305.0019 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0019, Box 28, Dvd 305.0019_a)
    Duration: 8 minutes
  - Bicentennial Time Capsules at Philadelphia, July 1978; ID: 305.0020 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0020, Box 28, Dvd 305.0020_a)
  - Bicentennial Time Capsules at Philadelphia, July 1978; ID: 305.0021 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0021, Box 28, Dvd 305.0021_a)
    Duration: 30 minutes
  - Helen Wheels at CBGB, September 23, 1978; ID: 305.0066 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0066, Box 28, Dvd 305.0066_a)
  - Dead Boys at Max's, March 1979; ID: 305.0022 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0022, Box 28, Dvd 305.0022_a)
  - Dead Boys at Max's, March 1979; ID: 305.0023 (Box 1, Media ID: 305.0023, Box 28, Dvd 305.0023_a)
    Duration: 17 minutes
  - Dead Boys at Max's, March 1979; ID: 305.0024 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0024, Box 28, Dvd 305.0024_a)
  - Dead Boys at Max's, March 1979; ID: 305.0025 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0025, Box 28, Dvd 305.0025_a)
    Duration: 20 minutes
  - Cuban Heels at CBGB, April 1979; ID: 305.0127 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0127, Box 31, Dvd 305.0127_a)
    Duration: 23 minutes
  - Desire at CBGB, April 1979; ID: 305.0026 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0026, Box 28, Dvd 305.0026_a)
  - Desire at CBGB, April 1979; ID: 305.0027 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0027, Box 28, Dvd 305.0027_a)
  - Stiletto Fads at CBGB, April 1979; ID: 305.0028 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0028, Box 28, Dvd 305.0028_a)
  - Stiletto Fads at CBGB, April 1979; ID: 305.0029 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0029, Box 28, Dvd 305.0029_a)
  - Ballistic Kisses at Danceteria, June 1979; ID: 305.0037 (Box 9, Media ID: 305.0037, Box 28, Dvd 305.0037_a)
    Duration: 34 minutes
  - Brainiacs at Mental Health Records, June 1979; ID: 305.0032 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0032, Box 28, Dvd 305.0032_a)
  - Brainiacs at Mental Health Records, June 1979; ID: 305.0119 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0119, Box 30, Dvd 305.0119_a)
    Alternate title: Brainiacs at Mental Health Records, June 1979 2/2
  - Dead Kennedys at Hurrah's, June 1979; ID: 305.0033 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0033, Box 28, Dvd 305.0033_a)
  - Dead Kennedys at Hurrahs, June 1979; ID: 305.0121 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0121, Box 31, Dvd 305.0121_a)
    Duration: 22 mimutes
    Alternate title: Dead Kennedys at Hurrahs, June 1979 2/2
  - Dils at Hurrah's, June 1979; ID: 305.0030 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0030, Box 28, Dvd 305.0030_a)
  - Dils at Hurrah's, June 1979; ID: 305.0031 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0031, Box 28, Dvd 305.0031_a)
  - Rock Against Racism - Crayola, Heat at Max's, June 1979; ID: 305.0034 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0034, Box 28, Dvd 305.0034_a)
  - Rock Against Racism - Stiletto's at Max's, June 1979; ID: 305.0036 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0036, Box 28, Dvd 305.0036_a)
  - Rock Against Racism - Unknown bands at Max's, June 1979; ID: 305.0035 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0035, Box 28, Dvd 305.0035_a)
    Format: DVD
    Duration: 00:21:54
  - Voidoids at CBGB, August 1979; ID: 305.0038 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0038, Box 28, Dvd 305.0038_a)
  - Voidoids at CBGB, August 1979; ID: 305.0039 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0039, Box 28, Dvd 305.0039_a)
    Duration: 00:07:52
  - Casulties at Max's, September 1979; ID: 305.0051 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0051, Box 29, Dvd 305.0051_a)
    Color/ Black & White, Sound
    Duration: 18 minutes
  - Destroy All Monsters at CBGB, September 1979; ID: 305.0041 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0041, Box 28, Dvd 305.0041_a)
  - Futants at CBGB, September 1979; ID: 305.0050 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0050, Box 29, Dvd 305.0050_a)
  - Heartbreakers at Max's, September 1979; ID: 305.0045 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0045, Box 29, Dvd 305.0045_a)
  - Heartbreakers at Max's, September 1979; ID: 305.0046 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0046, Box 29, Dvd 305.0046_a)
  - Heartbreakers at Max's, September 1979; ID: 305.0047 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0047, Box 29, Dvd 305.0047_a)
  - James "Blood" Ulmer at Danceteria, September 1979; ID: 305.0053 (Box 9, Media ID: 305.0053, Box 29, Dvd 305.0053_a)
    Duration: 40 minutes
  - Lounge Lizards at CBGB, September 1979; ID: 305.0048 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0048, Box 29, Dvd 305.0048_a)
  - Lounge Lizards, Futants at CBGB, September 1979; ID: 305.0049 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0049, Box 29, Dvd 305.0049_a)
  - Only Ones at CBGB, September 1979; ID: 305.0042 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0042, Box 29, Dvd 305.0042_a)
  - Only Ones at CBGB, September 1979; ID: 305.0043 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0043, Box 29, Dvd 305.0043_a)
    Duration: 10 minutes
    Original fDVD access copy available.ormat: 3/4" Umatic
  - Only Ones at CBGB, September 1979; ID: 305.0044 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0044, Box 29, Dvd 305.0044_a)
  - Revelons at CBGB, September 1979; ID: 305.0054 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0054, Box 29, Dvd 305.0054_a)
    Alternate title: Revelons at CBGB, September 1979 1/2
  - Revelons at CBGB, September 1979; ID: 305.0105 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0105, Box 29, Dvd 305.0105_a)
    Alternate title: Revelons at CBGBs, September 1979 2/2
  - Senders at The 80's, September 1979; ID: 305.0052 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0052, Box 29, Dvd 305.0052_a)
  - Levi / Rockats at CBGB, October 1979; ID: 305.0055 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0055, Box 29, Dvd 305.0055_a)
    Alternate title: Levi/Rockats at CBGB, October 1979 1/3
  - Levi and the Rockats at CBGB, October 1979; ID: 305.0056 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0056, Box 29, Dvd 305.0056_a)
    Alternate title: Levi and the Rockats at CBGBs, October 1979 2/3
  - Levi and the Rockats at CBGB, October 1979; ID: 305.0057 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0057, Box 29, Dvd 305.0057_a)
    Black & White and Color, Sound
    Duration: 11 minutes
    Alternate title: Levi and the Rockats at CBGBs, October 1979 3/3
  - Sick Dick and the Volkswagons at Max's, November 1979; ID: 305.0126 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0126, Box 31, Dvd 305.0126_a)
  - Wazmo Nariz at The 80's, November 1979; ID: 305.0058 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0058, Box 29, Dvd 305.0058_a)
  - Bad Brains at CBGB, December 1979; ID: 305.0107 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0107, Box 30, Dvd 305.0107_a)
    Duration: 31 minutes
  - Iggy Pop at Hurrah's, December 1979; ID: 305.0059 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0059, Box 29, Dvd 305.0059_a)
    Alternate title: Iggy Pop at Hurrah's, December 1979 2/2
  - Iggy Pop at Hurrah's, December 1979; ID: 305.0106 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0106, Box 30, Dvd 305.0106_a)
    Duration: 1 hour 3 minutes
    Alternate title: Iggy Pop at Hurrah's, December 1979 1/2
  - Our Daughters Wedding at Danceteria, December 1979; ID: 305.0060 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0060, Box 29, Dvd 305.0060_a)
    Duration: 35 minutes
  - 3 Teens Kill 4 at Peppermint Lounge, 1980; ID: 305.0123 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0123, Box 31, Dvd 305.0123_a)
    Duration: 15 minutes
  - Cheetah Chrome and the Casulaties at Max's, February 1980; ID: 305.0065 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0065, Box 29, Dvd 305.0065_a)
  - Colors at CBGB, February 1980; ID: 305.0061 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0061, Box 29, Dvd 305.0061_a)
    Alternate title: Colors at CBGB, February 1980 1/2
  - Colors at CBGB, February 1980; ID: 305.0062 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0062, Box 29, Dvd 305.0062_a)
    Alternate title: Colors at CBGB, February 1980 2/2
  - Pin-ups at CBGB, February 1980; ID: 305.0101 (Box 6, Media ID: 305.0101, Box 30, Dvd 305.0101_a)
  - Student Teachers at CBGB, Feburary 1980; ID: 305.0063 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0063, Box 29, Dvd 305.0063_a)
    Duration: 7 minutes
    Alternate title: Student Teachers at CBGB, Feburary 1980 1/2
  - Student Teachers at CBGB, Feburary 1980; ID: 305.0064 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0064, Box 29, Dvd 305.0064_a)
    Alternate title: Student Teachers at CBGB, Feburary 1980 2/2
  - Cramps at Irving Plaza, March 1980; ID: 305.0067 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0067, Box 29, Dvd 305.0067_a)
    Alternate title: Cramps at Irving Plaza, March 1980 1/3
  - Cramps at Irving Plaza, March 1980; ID: 305.0068 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0068, Box 29, Dvd 305.0068_a)
    Alternate title: Cramps at Irving Plaza, March 1980 2/3
  - Cramps at Irving Plaza, March 1980; ID: 305.0069 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0069, Box 29, Dvd 305.0069_a)
    Alternate title: Cramps at Irving Plaza, March 1980 3/3
  - Johnny Thunders & the Heartbreakers, John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980; ID: 305.0040 (Box 2, Media ID: 305.0040, Box 28, Dvd 305.0040_a)
    Alternate title: Heartbreakers, John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980 1/4
  - Joe King Carrasco at CBGB, March 1980; ID: 305.0070 (Box 3, Media ID: 305.0070, Box 29, Dvd 305.0070_a)
    Alternate title: Joe King Carrasco at CBGB, March 1980 1/2
  - Joe King Carrasco at CBGB, March 1980; ID: 305.0071 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0071, Box 29, Dvd 305.0071_a)
    Alternate title: Joe King Carrasco at CBGB, March 1980 2/2
  - John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980; ID: 305.0073 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0073, Box 29, Dvd 305.0073_a)
    Alternate title: John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980 2/4
  - John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980; ID: 305.0074 (Box 4, Media ID: 305.0074, Box 29, Dvd 305.0074_a)
    Alternate title: John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980 3/4
  - John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980; ID: 305.0075 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0075, Box 29, Dvd 305.0075_a)
    Alternate title: John Cale at Irving Plaza, March 1980 4/4
  - Rock Against Ratings: Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980; ID: 305.0077 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0077, Box 29, Dvd 305.0077_a)
    Duration: 19 minutes
    Alternate title: Rock Against Ratings: Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980 2/5
  - Rock Against Ratings: Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980; ID: 305.0078 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0078, Box 29, Dvd 305.0078_a)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Ratings: Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980 3/5
  - Rock Against Ratings: Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980; ID: 305.0079 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0079, Box 29, Dvd 305.0079_a)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Ratings: Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980 4/5
  - Rock Against Ratings: WPIX Band, Nuggets, Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980; ID: 305.0076 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0076, Box 29, Dvd 305.0076_a)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Ratings: WPIX Band, Nuggets, Heartbreakers at Irving Plaza, March 1980 1/5
  - Offs Go East at Mudd Club, April 1980; ID: 305.0125 (Box 7, Media ID: 305.0125, Box 31, Dvd 305.0125_a)
    Alternate title: Offs Go East at Mudd Club, April 1980 1/6
  - Offs Go East at Philly, April 1980; ID: 305.0080 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0080, Box 29, Dvd 305.0080_a)
    Alternate title: Offs Go East at Philly, April 1980 2/6
  - Offs Go East at Ambience, April 1980; ID: 305.0083 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0083, Box 30, Dvd 305.0083_a)
    Alternate title: Offs Go East at Philly, April 1980 5/6
  - Offs Go East at Ambience, April 1980; ID: 305.0084 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0084, Box 30, Dvd 305.0084_a)
    Alternate title: Offs Go East at Ambience, April 1980 6/6
  - Offs Go East at Rat Club, April 1980; ID: 305.0081 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0081, Box 29, Dvd 305.0081_a)
    Alternate title: Offs Go East at Philly, April 1980 3/6
  - Offs Go East at Rat Club, April 1980; ID: 305.0082 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0082, Box 30, Dvd 305.0082_a)
    Alternate title: Offs Go East at Philly, April 1980 4/6
  - Go-Go's and the Outsets at Danceteria, May 1980; ID: 305.0130 (Box 10, Media ID: 305.0130, Box 31, Dvd 305.0130_a)
  - Max Blagg at Danceteria, May 1980; ID: 305.0092 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0092, Box 30, Dvd 305.0092_a)
    Access DVD available.
  - Max Blagg at Danceteria, May 1980; ID: 305.0093 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0093, Box 30, Dvd 305.0093_a)
    Duration: 13 minutes
  - Rock Against Racism: Heat, Cigaretz, Bad Brains at Central Park, May 1980; ID: 305.0088 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0088, Box 30, Dvd 305.0088_a)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Racism: Stilettos, Casualties, Senders at Central Park, May 1980 3/5
  - Rock Against Racism: Lenny Kaye Band, Heat at Irving Plaza, May 1980; ID: 305.0085 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0085, Box 30, Dvd 305.0085_a)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Racism: Lenny Kaye Band, Heat at Irving Plaza, May 1980 5/5
  - Rock Against Racism: Mass Appeal, Jitters at Central Park, May 1980; ID: 305.0086 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0086, Box 30, Dvd 305.0086_a)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Racism: Mass Appeal, Jitters at Central Park, May 1980 1/5
  - Rock Against Racism: Senders at Central Park, May 1980; ID: 305.0090 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0090, Box 30, Dvd 305.0090_a)
  - Rock Against Racism: Stilettos, Casualties, Senders at Central Park, May 1980; ID: 305.0087 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0087, Box 30, Dvd 305.0087_a)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Racism: Stilettos, Casualties, Senders at Central Park, May 1980 2/5
  - Rock Against Racism: Terrorists, Panic Squad, Stilettos at Central Park, May 1980; ID: 305.0089 (Box 5, Media ID: 305.0089, Box 30, Dvd 305.0089_a)
    Alternate title: Rock Against Racism: Stilettos, Casualties, Senders at Central Park, May 1980 4/5